让我们来看看新闻发布会和莱昂内尔·斯卡洛尼。
Let's go with the press conference and Lionel Scaloni.
Vamos con la rueda de prensa y Lionel Scaloni.
问题是，当阅读比赛场上的情况时，只有一种阅读，比赛……
The thing is that when reading the situation on the playing field, there is only one reading, the game...
Es que la lectura de la situación del campo de juego, hay una sola lectura, el partido...
至少今天不符合参加比赛的条件，这是很明显的。
not meeting the conditions to play today at least, that's clear.
no reunir las condiciones para jugar hoy al menos, eso está claro.
然后就做出了决定...
Then the decision is made...
Después la decisión la toma...
让我们接受裁判，仅此而已。
Let's take the referee and that's it.
A tomar el árbitro y ya está.
显然，演出的条件，尤其是......
It is evident that the conditions for the show, especially...
Es evidente que las condiciones para el espectáculo, sobre todo...
阿南……
Anan...
我想多说点话，但我玩不了。
I want to talk a lot more, but I couldn't play.
Quiero hablar mucho más, pero no se podía jugar.
我们做了我们必须做的事情，无论是委内瑞拉还是阿根廷，但是条件......
We did what we had to do, both Venezuela and Argentina, but the conditions...
Hicimos lo que teníamos que hacer, tanto Venezuela como Argentina, pero las condiciones...
在坎波戈诺。
in Campo Gono.
en Campo Gono.
这不是一个这样级别的两选一秀，特别是因为它......
It wasn't for a two-selection show on the level of this, especially because it's...
no era para un espectáculo de dos selecciones del nivel de esto, sobre todo porque es...
周四比赛，我想明天就可以比赛。
Play Thursday, it could have been played tomorrow, I imagine.
Juega jueves, se podría haber jugado mañana, me imagino.
但这是另一点，当游戏不能玩时，它就不能玩
but that would be another point, when the game cannot be played, it cannot be played
pero eso ya sería otro punto más, cuando el partido no se puede jugar, no se puede jugar
晚上好，教授。
Good evening, professor.
Buenas noches, profesor.
晚安。
Good night.
Buenas noches.
安东尼奥
Antonio
首先，如果该党认为委内瑞拉有优势获胜，那么它会做出什么总体平衡？
Firstly, what general balance does the party make if it believes that, for example, Venezuela had the merits to win?
En primer lugar, ¿qué balance general hace el partido si cree que por ejemplo Venezuela reunió los méritos para ganar?
并向他询问战术情况，特别是莱昂纳多·瓦莱尔迪的加盟。
and ask him about a tactical situation in particular the entry of Leonardo Valerdi.
y preguntarle por una situación táctica en particular el ingreso de Leonardo Valerdi.
对不起，我不明白，因为我明白了一些事情，但不……他开始接近我。
Excuse me, but I don't understand because I understood some things, but no... He started to approach me.
Disculpa, pero no entiendo porque entendí algunas cosas, pero no... Me empezó a acercar.
不，但我不知道你是否接近。
No, but I don't know if you're close.
No, pero no sé si te acercas.
你现在听到我说话了吗？
Do you hear me now?
¿Me escucha ahora?
你能听得更清楚吗？
Can you hear me better?
¿Me escucha mejor?
首先
First of all
En primer lugar
例如，如果该党认为委内瑞拉有能力赢得三分，那么该党会做出什么总体平衡？
What general balance does the party make if it believes that Venezuela, for example, had the merits to win the three points?
¿Qué balance general hace el partido si cree que Venezuela reunió por ejemplo los méritos para ganarse los tres puntos?
而另一方面，阿根廷莱昂纳多·瓦莱尔迪加盟的具体情况，开始以三名中后卫出战，
and on the other hand, the specific situation of the entry of Leonardo Valerdi, Argentina began to play with three centre-backs,
y por otra parte, la situación puntual del ingreso de Leonardo Valerdi, Argentina pasó a jugar con tres centrales,
激活费尔南多·巴蒂斯塔决定派上的两名前锋，或者你在比赛中发现了一些特别的东西。
active the two forwards that Fernando Batista decided to enter or you identified something in particular in the game.
activo a los dos delanteros que decidió ingresar Fernando Batista o usted identificó algo en particular en el juego.
多谢。
Thanks a lot.
Muchísimas gracias.
好吧，我想象一下比赛的阅读，我认为最后的平局，我们也有几个。
Well, I imagine that the reading of the game, I think the tie at the end, we also had several.
Bueno, imagino que la lectura del partido, creo que el empate al final, nosotros también tuvimos varias.
很明显，他们从外面拿走了很多
quite clear, they have taken a lot from outside
bastante claras, ellos han tirado mucho de fuera
从禁区外他们打了很长时间的比赛
from outside the area they played long as the game had to be
de fuera del área han jugado en largo como tenía que ser el partido
考虑到他们的球员类型，我认为这场比赛由于他们的比赛方式而更加可行。
Due to the type of player they have, I think the match was more feasible due to the way they played.
por el tipo de jugador que tienen, el partido creo que estaba más factible por su manera de jugar
Leo 的进入是因为从逻辑上讲
and Leo's entry was because logically
y la entrada de Leo fue porque lógicamente
他们有两名前锋。
They had two forwards.
Ellos tenían dos delanteros.
尽管在进球数上我们也不错，但我们处于平局，而且都没有
although numerically in the goal play we were also good, we were on parity and neither
aunque numericamente en la jugada del gol también estábamos bien, estábamos paridad y tampoco
这也不是看那里的问题。
It's not a question of looking there either.
tampoco es cuestión de mirar ahí.
所以，好吧，在莱安德罗条目的开头，对不起，莱昂纳多，就是为了这个。
So, well, at the beginning of Leandro's entry, sorry Leonardo, it was for that.
Así que, bueno, al principio de la entrada de Leandro, perdón de Leonardo, fue para eso.
请。
please.
por favor.
这里
Here
Acá
花了近两年的时间才获得这个称号
It took almost two years to obtain the title of
pasaron casi dos años de obtención del título del
距离下一届世界杯也只有不到两年的时间了。
also less than two years away from the next World Cup.
también a menos de dos años casi del próximo Mundial.
除了今天的比赛之外，本次双预选赛结束后，阿根廷队肯定会成为领先者。
Beyond today's match, Argentina will surely be the leader after this double qualifying round.
más allá del partido de hoy, Argentina va a quedar puntero seguramente después de esta doble fecha de eliminatorias.
世界杯结束后的这两年你感觉如何？这对球队进步的基础有何影响？
How do you feel in these two years that passed after the World Cup and how does it form the basis of the team's progress?
¿Cómo te sentís vos en estos dos años que pasaron después del Mundial y cómo da el base del progreso del equipo?
进行了一些修改，了解了美洲锦标赛的情况。
with the modifications, with what was happening with the Bicampeonato de América.
con las modificaciones, con lo que fue pasando con el Bicampeonato de América.
用什么？
With what?
¿Con la qué?
请原谅我，因为我真的不太了解你。
Forgive me, because if I don't understand you little, really.
Perdóname, porque si no te entiendo poco, de verdad.
对不起。
Sorry.
Perdón.
以及在这个过程中你如何评价...
and how do you evaluate in this process...
y cómo evaluás en este proceso...
两年来，团队。
of the two years, the team.
de los dos años, el equipo.
首先，你的感受和团队的演变。
First, how you feel and the evolution of the team.
Primero, cómo te sentís vos y la evolución del equipo.
好吧，我们看看，需要评估的是条件，而不是比赛之外。
Well, let's see, what needs to be evaluated is the conditions, not beyond the match.
Bueno, a ver, lo que hay que valorar es las condiciones, no más allá del partido.
今天的比赛，我们拿出今天的比赛，南美区预选赛的情况。
today's game, we take out today's game, the conditions of the South American qualifiers.
el partido de hoy, sacamos el partido de hoy, las condiciones de las eliminatorias sudamericanas.
所以我们适应...
So we adapt to...
Entonces nosotros nos adaptamos a...
尽管遇到了所有的困难，但球队总是在竞争。
with all the difficulties it has and the team always competes.
con todas las dificultades que tiene y el equipo compite siempre.
然后，从逻辑上讲，正如我们常说的，你可以为这支球队打得更好或更差。
Then, logically, as we always say, you can play better or worse for this team.
después, lógicamente, como siempre decimos, se puede jugar mejor o peor para este equipo.
我觉得和皮蒂...
I think with Pitti...
Creo que con Pitti...
我不知道是否应该称之为进化，但在竞争层面上，我认为我们做得很好，我们增加了许多离开他们的年轻人......
I don't know whether to call it evolution, but at a competitive level I think we are doing well, we are adding many young guys who are leaving their...
no sé si llamarlo evolución, pero a nivel competitivo creo que estamos bien, estamos sumando muchos chicos jóvenes que se van su...
来看这些预选赛，看看我们谁可以做出贡献
coming to see these qualifying matches and for us who can contribute
viniendo a ver estos partidos de eliminatoria y para nosotros que puedan aportar
和我们在一起是一种快乐。
Being here with us is a joy.
estando acá con nosotros es una alegría.
布埃诺。
Bueno.
晚上好，埃斯卡罗尼老师，
Good evening teacher Escaloni,
Buenas noches profe Escaloni,
阿根廷 88.1 FM。
88.1 FM of Argentina.
88.1 FM de Argentina.
在下半场。
in the second half.
en el segundo tiempo.
贡萨洛·蒙蒂尔（Gonzalo Montiel）换下蒂亚戈·阿尔马达（Tiago Almada），这样我们在第二节就有了五名后卫
the entry of Gonzalo Montiel for Tiago Almada so that this gave us five defenders in the second
el ingreso de Gonzalo Montiel por Tiago Almada de modo de que esto nos daba a cinco defensores en la segunda
另一方面，考虑到这
On the other hand, consider that this
por parte, considera que este
下半场委内瑞拉队获得最多机会，最终扳平比分。
It conditioned that second half in which Venezuela had the greatest number of chances and where Venezuela achieved the tie.
condicionó ese segundo tiempo en el que Venezuela tuvo mayor cantidad de ocasiones y donde Venezuela consigue el empate.
不，我们一开始比赛时并没有五名后卫。
No, we did not start playing with five defenders.
No, no pasamos a jugar con cinco defensores.
从来没有，一刻也没有，直到瓦勒迪进来。
Never, not for a moment, until Valerdi entered.
Nunca, ni un momento, hasta que entró Valerdi.
我们总是四个人一起玩。
We always play with four.
Siempre jugamos con cuatro.
老师您好，您好吗？
Hello teacher, how are you?
Hola profe, ¿cómo está?
晚上好，来自 El Universal 的 Rubén Hernández。
Good evening, Rubén Hernández from El Universal.
Muy buenas noches, Rubén Hernández de El Universal.
嗯，我的问题是这样的。
Well, my question is this.
Bueno, mi pregunta es la siguiente.
你是否认为尽管这场比赛很有趣、很美味……
Do you consider that even though the match was quite interesting, tasty...
¿Usted considera que a pesar de que el partido fue bastante interesante, sabrosito...
你想和委内瑞拉队一起参加世界杯吗？
Would you like to play with Venezuela in the World Cup?
¿Le gustaría jugar con Venezuela en el Mundial?
与委内瑞拉进行一场正面交锋？
Meet Venezuela in a head-to-head match?
¿Encontrarse con Venezuela en un partido cara a cara?
太感谢了。
Thank you so much.
Muchas gracias.
我希望委内瑞拉能够首先晋级，因为......
I would love for Venezuela to qualify first because...
Me encantaría primero que Venezuela clasifique porque...
除了教练组的成员之外，我们也非常感谢他。
In addition to the people on the coaching staff, we have a lot of appreciation for him.
Además de la gente del cuerpo técnico, le tenemos mucho aprecio.
我特别喜欢委内瑞拉人民，希望他们能够晋级世界杯。
I particularly love the Venezuelan people and I hope they can qualify for the World Cup.
A la gente venezolana particularmente le tengo cariño y ojalá pueda clasificar el Mundial.
他们应得的，人们应得的，他们的比赛方式应得的，我希望他们能稍后再去。
They deserve it, the people deserve it, the way they are playing deserves it and I hope they can go later.
que lo merece, lo merece la gente, lo merece la manera que están jugando y ojalá puedan ir después.
如果轮到我们了，我们也必须晋级，我们拭目以待。
and if it's our turn we have to qualify too, we'll see.
y si nos toca tenemos que clasificar nosotros también, ya veremos.
谢谢老师，谢谢大家。
Thank you teacher, thank you all.
Gracias profe, gracias a todos.
谢谢。
Gracias.